Menu

### Pronunciator Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for https://www.pronunciator.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 

2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.   

3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 

4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing** 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via registration, email or other direct contact from you. 

We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.   

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization.   

Unless you ask us to, we will _not_ contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.   

**Registration** 

In order to track progress and quiz scores in the Pronunciator App, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give a valid email address. This information is used to identify you if you contact us for technical support, and to help you retrieve your login credentials if you misplace them. 

**Personalized Courses** 

When you create a personalized course, we will ask you for details including your interests, your occupation, your age range, your language skill level, your email address (optional), and whether you want to use your computer microphone (optional) and/or webcam (optional) within the personalized courses that you create. This information is used exclusively for the purpose of creating your personalized course, is not used for any other purpose, and is not disclosed to any third party. If you do not wish to provide these details, we encourage you to use the non-personalized areas (e.g. the Main Course, the Learning Guides, etc.) of Pronunciator that do not require this information. 

**Cookies** 

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information** 

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

• See what data we have about you, if any. 

• Change/correct any data we have about you. 

• Have us delete any data we have about you. 

• Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Security** 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as email address and chosen password), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.   

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

 If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 307-203-2151 or via email: support@pronunciator.com     

Copyright 2011- 2024 Pronunciator LLC
